<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/</link><description>Recent content on Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:20:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-jimm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-jimm/</guid><description>Oral presentation at 2022 JIM Fall Meeting I presented at the session, &amp;ldquo;Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys (VIII)&amp;rdquo; in 2022 Japan Institute of Metals and Materials Fall Meeting.
Deformation behavior of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloys at room temperature
Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Nozomi Ueyama, Yorinobu Takigawa.
2022 Japan Institute of Metals and Materials Fall Meeting, Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys (VIII), S1.20，Fukuoka．</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-photochem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-photochem/</guid><description>Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022 Research findings of collaborative research have been presented in Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022.
Laser ablation synthesis of FeCoNi medium entropy alloy colloidal solution by using high-repetition rate UV picosecond laser
Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi, Atsuya Watanabe．
Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022 ,1P26, Kyoto.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2207-srep/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2207-srep/</guid><description>New paper has been published on SciRep Tensile strength of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy fabricated using electrodeposition
A. Watanabe, T. Yamamoto, and Y. Takigawa
Scientific Reports, 12, 12076 (2022).
doi: 10.1038/s41598-022-16086-6
Tensile strength of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy fabricated using electrodeposition</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2204-fellowship/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2204-fellowship/</guid><description>Receiving a fellowship I adopted as a student for &amp;ldquo;Fellowship Program to Foster International Ph.D.-Holding Researchers through Materials Innovations&amp;rdquo; by Japan Science and Technology Agency (Grant Number JPMJFS2138)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2204-omu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2204-omu/</guid><description>Graduated from a master&amp;rsquo;s course and Entering a doctoral course. I graduated from a master&amp;rsquo;s course at Department of Materials Science, Graduate School of Osaka Prefecture University.
And I entered a doctoral course at Department of Materials Science, Graduate School of Engineering, Osaka Metropolitan University
I continue a participant in Graduate Course for System-Inspired Leaders in Multidisciplinary Science (SiMS).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2203-jim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2203-jim/</guid><description>I took an oral presentation at the spring meeting of the Japan Inst. Metals and Materials.
A. Watanabe, T. Yamamoto, R. Miyamoto, Y. Takigawa.
Electrodeposition of bcc FeCoNi medium entropy alloy with fine grains
The spring meeting of the Japan Inst. Metals and Materials Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys VII, S2.26, on-line.</description></item><item><title>Introduction movie for our laboratory on YouTube</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/video/2109-youtube/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/video/2109-youtube/</guid><description>A laboratory I am belonging has been introduced on a YouTube channel of Osaka Metropolitan University.
(in Japanese only&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2011-rsurfi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2011-rsurfi/</guid><description>A paper has been published as a first paper on RSURFI Reducing sulfur to improve thermal embrittlement in electrodeposited nickel using citric acid
A. Watanabe, Y. Takigawa
Results in Surfaces and Interfaces, 1, 1000001 (2020).（査読有り）
doi: 10.1016/j.rsurfi.2020.100001
This paper was selected as a Highlighted Article and featured on the journal page.
Reducing sulfur to improve thermal embrittlement in electrodeposited nickel using citric acid</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2003_scirep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2003_scirep/</guid><description>A paper was published on Sci. Rep. Microstructural heterogeneity in the electrodeposited Ni: insights from growth modes
I. Matsui, A. Watanabe, Y. Takigawa, N. Omura, T. Yamamoto
Sci. Rep., 10, 5548 (2020). doi: 10.1038/s41598-020-62565-z
Microstructural heterogeneity in the electrodeposited Ni: insights from growth modes</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/1909-mtla/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/1909-mtla/</guid><description>A paper was published on MTLA Mechanical properties and microstructures after abnormal grain growth in electrodeposited Ni–W alloys
I. Matsui, A. Watanabe, T. Uesugi, N. Omura, Y. Takigawa , T. Yamamoto
Materialia, 8, 100481 (2019). doi: 10.1016/j.mtla.2019.100481
Mechanical properties and microstructures after abnormal grain growth in electrodeposited Ni–W alloys</description></item></channel></rss>