<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Paper on Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/categories/paper/</link><description>Recent content in Paper on Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/categories/paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2303-jalcom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2303-jalcom/</guid><description>New paper has been published on JALCOM! Fabrication of FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy nanoparticles by high-repetition-rate UV picosecond laser ablation in water
Atsuya Watanabe, Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi
Journal of Alloys and Compounds (in press).
10.1016/j.jallcom.2023.169896</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2303-ymst/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2303-ymst/</guid><description>New paper has been published on MST Microstructure and tensile strength of electrodeposited Fe-rich bcc FeCoNi medium-entropy alloys
A. Watanabe, T. Yamamoto, R. Miyamoto, and Y. Takigawa
Materials Science and Technology (in press).
10.1080/02670836.2023.2187973</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2207-srep/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2207-srep/</guid><description>New paper has been published on SciRep Tensile strength of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy fabricated using electrodeposition
A. Watanabe, T. Yamamoto, and Y. Takigawa
Scientific Reports, 12, 12076 (2022).
doi: 10.1038/s41598-022-16086-6
Tensile strength of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy fabricated using electrodeposition - Scientific Reports</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2011-rsurfi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2011-rsurfi/</guid><description>A paper has been published as a first paper on RSURFI Reducing sulfur to improve thermal embrittlement in electrodeposited nickel using citric acid
A. Watanabe, Y. Takigawa
Results in Surfaces and Interfaces, 1, 1000001 (2020).（査読有り）
doi: 10.1016/j.rsurfi.2020.100001
This paper was selected as a Highlighted Article and featured on the journal page.
Better and more attractive nickel plating: A technique that removes sulphur from the nickel plating process maintains ductility at higher temperatures and enhances visual appeal</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2003_scirep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2003_scirep/</guid><description>A paper was published on Sci. Rep. Microstructural heterogeneity in the electrodeposited Ni: insights from growth modes
I. Matsui, A. Watanabe, Y. Takigawa, N. Omura, T. Yamamoto
Sci. Rep., 10, 5548 (2020). doi: 10.1038/s41598-020-62565-z
Microstructural heterogeneity in the electrodeposited Ni: insights from growth modes - Scientific Reports</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/1909-mtla/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/1909-mtla/</guid><description>A paper was published on MTLA Mechanical properties and microstructures after abnormal grain growth in electrodeposited Ni–W alloys
I. Matsui, A. Watanabe, T. Uesugi, N. Omura, Y. Takigawa , T. Yamamoto
Materialia, 8, 100481 (2019). doi: 10.1016/j.mtla.2019.100481</description></item></channel></rss>