<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>works on 渡邉充哉</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/tags/works/</link><description>Recent content in works on 渡邉充哉</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:00:29 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atsuyaw.github.io/tags/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Paper</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/page/papers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:00:29 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/page/papers/</guid><description>researchmapも併せてご覧ください。
Research article 2023-07-25 Fabrication of FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy nanoparticles by high-repetition-rate UV picosecond laser ablation in water Atsuya Watanabe, Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi Journal of Alloys and Compounds, 950, 169896 (2023). 10.1016/j.jallcom.2023.169896 Research Article 2023-03-15 Microstructure and tensile strength of electrodeposited Fe-rich bcc FeCoNi medium-entropy alloys Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Ryousuke Miyamoto, Yorinobu Takigawa Materials Science and Technology, 39, 2028-2034 (2023). 10.1080/02670836.2023.2187973 Article 2022-07-15 Tensile strength of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy fabricated using electrodeposition Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Yorinobu Takigawa Scientific Reports, 12, 12076 (2022).</description></item><item><title>Presentation</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/page/presentations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 17:17:59 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/page/presentations/</guid><description>researchmapも併せてご覧ください。
予定 Grain growth bihavior in electrodeposited nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy
Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Koichiro Nambu, Yorinobu Takigawa
IFHTSE2023, Yokohama, 2023-11-15. 2023 めっき法によるバルクナノ結晶FeCoNiミディアムエントロピー合金の創製
渡邉充哉, 山本剛久, 瀧川順庸
第30回機械材料・材料加工技術講演会(M&amp;amp;amp;P2023)，つくば， 2023-09-28.
Development of high-strength bulk nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy via electrodeposition
Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Yorinobu Takigawa
大阪公立大学 工学研究科国際シンポジウム，大阪，2023-09-20．
水中レーザーアブレーションによるコアシェル型FeCoNiミディアムエントロピー合金ナノ粒子の鎖状構造形成
八ツ橋知幸, 渡邉充哉
光化学討論会，広島， 2023-09-06．
Fabrication of FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy nanoparticles by high-repetition-rate UV picosecond laser ablation in water
Atsuya Watanabe, ◦Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi.</description></item></channel></rss>