<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Meeting on Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</title><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/categories/meeting/</link><description>Recent content in Meeting on Atsuya Watanabe's Personal Web-site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/categories/meeting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2302-inthea/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2302-inthea/</guid><description>HEA Internatinal Workship Prof. Yatsuhashi at Dept. Science, Osaka Metropolitan University presented the findings in our collaborative research.
Fabrication of FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy by laser ablation in water using UV picosecond laser pulses
Atsuya Watanabe, Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi．
HEA International Workshop, Kyoto, 2023-02-14,15.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2211-jimmtexture/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2211-jimmtexture/</guid><description>Oral presentetion I presented at the society for crystal orientation and crystal direction analysis technologies.
Crystal orientation changes in electrodeposited nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloy Atsuya Watanabe，Yorinobu Takigawa．
Japan Intitute of metals and materials, 1st society for crystal orientation and crystal direction analysis technologies, 4, Atami, 2022-11-25.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-jimm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-jimm/</guid><description>Oral presentation at 2022 JIM Fall Meeting I presented at the session, &amp;ldquo;Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys (VIII)&amp;rdquo; in 2022 Japan Institute of Metals and Materials Fall Meeting.
Deformation behavior of nanocrystalline FeCoNi medium-entropy alloys at room temperature
Atsuya Watanabe, Takahisa Yamamoto, Nozomi Ueyama, Yorinobu Takigawa.
2022 Japan Institute of Metals and Materials Fall Meeting, Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys (VIII), S1.20，Fukuoka.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-photochem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2209-photochem/</guid><description>Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022 Research findings of collaborative research have been presented in Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022.
Laser ablation synthesis of FeCoNi medium entropy alloy colloidal solution by using high-repetition rate UV picosecond laser
Tomoyuki Yatsuhashi, Atsuya Watanabe．
Annual Meeting on Photochemistry 2022 ,1P26, Kyoto.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2203-jim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://atsuyaw.github.io/en/status/2203-jim/</guid><description>I took an oral presentation at the spring meeting of the Japan Inst. Metals and Materials.
A. Watanabe, T. Yamamoto, R. Miyamoto, Y. Takigawa.
Electrodeposition of bcc FeCoNi medium entropy alloy with fine grains
The spring meeting of the Japan Inst. Metals and Materials Materials Science and Technology in High-Entropy Alloys VII, S2.26, on-line.</description></item></channel></rss>